Many among us spend a considerable part of our lives working – with many of us, these days, working from home.
我们中的许多人一生中相当一部分时间都在工作，如今，越来越多的人选择居家办公。
While there are many benefits offered by not going to the office – not commuting, avoiding the rat race, and not having to panic about getting a seat if you hot-desk – there are also what some would call sacrifices.
居家办公的好处有很多，不用通勤、避开激烈的职场竞争，也不用在开放式办公模式下为抢占工位而焦虑，但与此同时，也有人认为这需要我们做出一些牺牲。
No more coffees with colleagues, chit-chats by the water cooler or going out for team-bonding meals.
我们再也不能和同事一起喝咖啡、在茶水间闲聊，或是外出参加团建聚餐了。
So, seeing as we rarely meet these people, why is it still important to be friends with those we work with?
既然我们很少和这些人见面，那么与同事建立友好关系为什么依然很重要呢？
Well, some reasons are obvious – working with like-minded people who you get on with can make those hours at work more fruitful and positive.
原因其实显而易见，和志同道合、相处融洽的人共事，能让工作时光变得更有成效、更积极愉悦。
Various situations are commonplace in the job you do, so having people to talk to about the intricacies of tasks could make your life easier.
工作中难免会遇到各种各样的常见状况，有可以倾诉任务细节的人，能让你的工作生活轻松不少。
It’s also nice knowing that you can have banter or a chinwag with people at work – and some of your colleagues may become friends in your life outside of the 9-5.
能和同事们开开玩笑、闲聊几句，也是一件很惬意的事，而且有些同事还可能会成为你工作之外的朋友。
But it’s not just to the benefit of the person; it’s also good for the company you work for.
但这不仅对个人有益，对你所在的公司同样有好处。
According to Dr Emma Seppala, people who said they had friends at work were more productive, had higher levels of retention and were more satisfied with their jobs than those who didn’t.
艾玛·塞帕拉博士的研究表明，称自己在工作中有朋友的人，相比没有职场朋友的人，工作效率更高、留任意愿更强，对工作的满意度也更高。
And what can happen if you don’t connect – if you don’t stimulate your relationships with those who do the same job as you?
如果你疏于和同事建立联系，不去维护职场人际关系，会发生什么呢？
While it can be easy to avoid them physically, Dr Adam Hickman says that feelings of social isolation and loneliness may creep in.
虽然你可以轻易地在物理层面避开他们，但亚当·希克曼博士表示，社交孤立和孤独感可能会悄然而至。
It makes sense – according to Maslow’s hierarchy of needs, a psychological theory which tries to explain human behaviour and motivation based on necessities, a feeling of belonging is one of the strongest psychological needs.
这是有道理的，马斯洛需求层次理论是一种基于人类基本需求来解释人类行为和动机的心理学理论，该理论指出，归属感是人类最强烈的心理需求之一。
No one wants to be where they feel unwanted, which is why many companies try to stimulate workplace interaction – be it ping pong tables in the office, or online parties.
没有人愿意待在一个不被接纳的地方，这也是许多公司想方设法促进职场互动的原因——无论是在办公室里摆放乒乓球桌，还是举办线上派对。
And finally, even though we’re working more from home now, we may one day see our colleagues once again.
最后，尽管我们现在更多时候都在居家办公，但总有一天我们可能会再次和同事见面。
Having a good relationship with them would make that meeting much more pleasant.
与他们保持良好的关系，会让重逢变得更加愉快。
So, if you’ve burned your bridges, it might be time to start mending them.
所以，如果你之前和同事闹僵了、自断了后路，或许现在是时候修复这些关系了。